as well as creating word documents from
scratch there may be occasions where you
wish to use a pre-formatted template
this could be for a cv poster flyer
newsletter
or even a letter template to access the
templates
you would simply need to go to the file
menu click on fail and then select new
from template
once you've clicked on that it will open
up the template box
this will allow you to select from a
wide range of templates
and as you can see a blank document is
still a template because it has
pre-formatting applied such as the font
the font size the borders margins etc
other templates available as you can see
are notes as calendar templates
there's cover letters there are cvs
there's journals newsletters brochures
and leaflet templates
so once you've selected the template
that you wish to use you would simply
double click on that and then that will
open up in word
and once the document is open in word
you would then be able to
add your title and then change the text
as you can see the text is already in
there so it just allows you to
go in click on each section and then you
could change the text within there
the thing to remember with template is
it will automatically apply
the formatting in that section that is
already on there so
in this section the title the title is
times new room and 39
so whatever you type in there it will
automatically apply the times new room
and 39
and other various formatting options
will automatically be applied
so that's always something to remember
that if you want to use a template
it can't be difficult to make changes to
the template
if it isn't suitable for your purpose